Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Carl - and 8-year-old son,undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Chas. and Wife,undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Emory T. - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Gerald - and Wife,June 7, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Gerald T.,undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Gladys - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Harold - 2 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, J.P.,undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Larry - 11-month-old,undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Lorraine,undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Mary,September 7, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Orville - H.S.,January 7, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Ralph - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Smith, Robert - I.D., Charlie's Son,undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Sneathen, George E. - Copy of Central Michigan College of Education Transcript,undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Snyder, Janet - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Sogamall, Paula Chi,undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, South, Agnes - Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, South, Agnes - Boy and Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spagnoula, Frank (Mrs.) - Copy of Daughter,undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spence, Sandra - 4 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spencer, Dick - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spencer, Donna - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spencer, Evelyn - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spencer, Roy,undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spillman, James (Mrs.),undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Spiris, Geo.,undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Sponseller, Geo. - 4 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stacy, G.,undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Staley, Don - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stamm, Carl,undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stamm, Jake,undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stamm, John - Saw Mill, Blanchard,August 25, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stanley, Eva,undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stebleton, J. - Baby,undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stevens, Lucy - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stewart, William - Wedding,undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stokes, Jerry,undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Straka, Emma - 2 Boys and Mother,undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Straley, Robt.,undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Strange, Robert,undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Straus, Max -14-month-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Strehl, Harry - and Wife,February 19,1968 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Streng, Fred - 2-year-old Girl,October 19,1968 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Strong, Alson,undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Stroup, Joyce,undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Sutton, Jan,undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Swain, Linda - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Swan, Alice Dowell,undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Swan, Bob - Baby Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Swan, Francis, Jr. - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Swan, Mrs. H.,undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Swett, Joy,undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Sytek, Theodor,undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tate, Harry - Copy of Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tayler, Lewis - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Taylor, Nick - I.D.,1956 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thayer, Wallace,undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theilen, Betty - and Mrs. Gunderman, I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theilen, Peter - Family,undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theisen, Bob - Wedding (Mary Lou Loreny),undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theisen, Dianne,undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theisen, Dorothy,undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theisen, H.,undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theisen, Jack - (3),November 23, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Theisen, John - 9-month-old,April 13, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thering, Bill - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thering, Elmer (3 Soldiers),undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thering, Helen,undated (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thering, John,October 20, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thering, Marilyn - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Therman, A. -1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thielen, Don - Copy of Chiropractic Letter,August 28, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thomas, Larry - 3-month-old,1963 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thompkins, Russ (Mrs.) - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Thorn, Sharon - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilman, Roy - Copy of 1928 Photograph,undated (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilman, Roy - Children; 3-, 5-, and 11-year-olds,undated (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilman, Roy - 3-year-old Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilmann, Roy - 4-year-old Boy,1959 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilmann, Roy - 1st Communion, Boy,May 1962 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilmann, Roy - 1st Communion, Girl,May 4, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tilmann, Roy - 1-year-old Girl,July 28, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Todd, Bud - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Torpey, Leo - 1-year-old,undated (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Torpey, Susan,undated (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Torres, Dan - 14-month-old,undated (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Trainor, Jack - Baby Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Travis, H.,undated (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Travis, Kenneth,undated (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Travis, Kenneth - Wedding,undated (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Traylor, [no first name] (Mrs.),undated (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Trevisiol, Carol - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tromblay, Arthur - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Tromblay, Effie - I.D.,February 28, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Trumbley, E. (Mrs.),undated (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Twindlehurst, Jeaneen,undated (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Ulbrich, John (Mrs.),undated (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Ulbrich, John - and Wife,undated (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Underland,undated (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Urmerback, Rudy,undated (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanArker, Harry - and Wife,undated (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Vanderwoude, Louise,undated (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanHorn, Forrest - Family 4, Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanHorn, Fred - 1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanHorn, Fred - Wedding,undated (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanLiew, M. - 2 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanNostrand, Howard - Wedding,undated (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanOmmeran, C. (Three Group),undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanOrden, Betty,undated (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VanOrden, Shirley - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Vanzo, Ralph Bruce - Copy of Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Varga, Violet - (Couple, Bridesmaid),undated (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Verrette, Ethyl - Copy of Marriage License,April 29, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Verwey, Andrew - (Mr. and Mrs.),April 22, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Verwey, Joe,undated (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Verwey, John -3 Boys,undated (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Verwey, Marinus - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Vodicka, Robert - 1.5 -year-old Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Vogel, Joseph - Weidman R #1, Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Voisen, Ed (Mrs.),August 18, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Voisin, Ed,undated (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Voisin, Norma,undated (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, VonDoloski, Walter - 5- and 7-year-old Boys,undated (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Waiversik, Ed and Wife,July 21, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Walker, Ann - 2 Children,December 2, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wallace, Billie Lee - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wallace, Mary - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Walters, Marcella,undated (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Walton, James - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Ward, Bob,undated (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Ward, Esther - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Ward, Roger - (1 and 2) 1-year-old,1963 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Warner, Bob - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Warner, Ronald -2 Children 2.5- and 3.5-year-olds,undated (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Watson, Don- and Anne Mayville,undated (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Watson, Lloyd,undated (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Watson, Sally,undated (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wattelet, Ray,undated (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weaver, Al - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weaver, Jess -2-year-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weaver, Jess,undated (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weaver, Ken - 10-month-old,undated (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weaver, Kim - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weeke, Clayton - Mr. and Mrs.,undated (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wehrly, Clarice,undated (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weipert, John - 50th Anniversary,undated (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Welsh, Jim - Blanchard, Michigan - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wentworth, Dick - 5 Children,1962 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wentworth, Richard - 2-year-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wermette, Dan - 3 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wernette, M.J. - Grandpa and 3 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wert, Dale (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Westbrook, Jack - 3-year-old Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Westie, Chas. - Wife and Daughter,March 26, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Weston, Kenneth - Baby Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wezensky, Ann - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wezensky, Helen - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Whaley, Earl - Copy of Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wheaton, Louise,undated (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Whitney, Bob,undated (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Whitney, Doris,undated (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Whitney, Wm. - 50th Anniversary,undated (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Whittier, L.,undated (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wicks, John - Couple,undated (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wicks, Murray - Couple,undated (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilberg, [no first name] (Mrs.),undated (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilcox, Jerrie - 1-year-old Boy,March 12, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilcox, Jerry - 7-month-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilcox, Jimmy - Copy of Christmas Card,undated (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilcox, Richard,undated (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilcox, Ruth - 4-year-old Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wiley, George Alvin - Copy of Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wiley, Jerry - Copy,November 19, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Williams, G. - Family,undated (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Williams, John - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Williamson, John - Couple,undated (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilmat, James - Wedding,undated (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilmout, Joe - 2 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Aletha - 3 Children,undated (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Joan,undated (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, John and Wife,undated (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Luciele,undated (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Pat,December 7, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Richard E. - 14-month-old,June 19, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Roy,undated (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilson, Tom - 7-month-old,undated (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wilt, Ted - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Winder, R. - Trooper,undated (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Winesburgh, Geo.,undated (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wonsey, Geo. - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wood, Chas. - Baby,undated (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wood, Kathryn - 1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wood, W.D. - Copy,undated (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Woodburg, Tom - H.S.,undated (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Woodin, Loretta Allen,undated (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Woods, Helen,undated (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Woods, Lewis - Family,undated (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Woods, Mike,undated (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wooster, Don,undated (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Wright, Joe - 45th Anniversary,undated (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yaeger, Ione - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yoder, Gene - Copy,June 9, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yoder, Rochel,undated (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yost, Carl (Mrs.),undated (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yost, Harry - I.D.,undated (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Young, Sylvia,undated (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Young, Sylvia (Mrs.),September 23, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Youngs, Jess - Son - Air Force,undated (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yunker, F. - Baby,undated (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yunkers, Arlene,undated (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yunkers, Herbert - Family,undated (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yunkers, Herbert - Boy, 1st Communion,undated (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Yunkers, Richard - Wedding,undated (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Zarks, Ben - Baby Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Zeien, L. - 4-year-old Girl,undated (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Zuker, Ed - Copy of Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Zuker, Frank - and Wife,November 1967 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Zuker, Helen,undated (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z, Zygmond, Gloria,undated (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbey, Ron and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Donald W. - I.D. (2 envelopes),July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Marshall, Sr. (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Marshall (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Marshall - Girl (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Marshall and Wife (2 envelopes),Christmas 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Mickey - 2 Children (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Abbot, Wayne -4 Children,undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Achenback, Paul,June 21, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Achenback, Paul (Mrs.),June 23, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Acher, Donna (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ackerman, C. (3 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Adams, Shirley - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Alban, Art (3 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Albar, Al (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Albar, Art - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Albee, J.A. - Baby Girl (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Albee, Jack - Mother,undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Albee, Jack - Daughter,undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Aldrick, J.C. - 1-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Aldrick, J.C. - 4-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Aldrick, J.C. - 1- and 4-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Aleman, Martin - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Alexander, Clara - Aunt,undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Alexander, Evelyn,undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Alexander Family,undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Donna - 2-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Donna,undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Katie,undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Leona,undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Loretta - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Marjorie,undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Treva - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Allen, Willard - Copy of Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Anderson, Dale - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Anne [no surname],undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Armstrong, Janet - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Army Years,undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ash, Alvin - 1-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ash, Alvin - 1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ash, Alvin - 1- and 2-year-old Children (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ash, Alvin - 1-year-old,September 1961 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ash, Shirley - 1-year-old,March 5, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ashivarth, Lucille,April 1, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ashivarth, Lucille - Daughter,April 1, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ashquab, Rosie - Copies,undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Asiala, Roger,undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Askegard, Harry - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Askegard, Harry - 1- and 2-year-olds,March 21,1964 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Askegard, H.L. - 3 Babies,July 19, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Askegard, Mildred - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Askegard, Shirley - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barney, Ruth H.,November 11, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barrett, Clarence (2),undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barrett, Joyce,undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barrett, Marlene,undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barry, Richard - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barton, Fred - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Barton, Phylis,undated (Box 4, Folder 59)